Guide to the American Association of Family and Consumer Sciences records, 1899-2008.
American Association of Family and Consumer Sciences records,
- Series V. Professional and Subject-Matter Groups
  - Food and Nutrition
    - Speeches and papers, 1932, 1961-1967 (Box 190)
    - Newsletters, 1961-1962 (Box 190)
    - Annual meeting, 1982 (Box 190)
    - Annual meeting, 1984; 2 folders (Box 190)
    - Financial reports, 1982-1984 (Box 190)
    - Correspondence, 1981-1983; 2 folders (Box 190)
    - Nutrition Education workshop, 1981 (Box 190)
    - Correspondence, 1982-1983 (Box 190)
    - Pre-Annual Meeting workshop, 1983 (Box 190)
    - Pre-Annual Meeting workshop, 1985 (Box 190)
    - Nutrition Education workshop, 1977 (Box 190)
    - Questionnaire, 1971 (Box 190)
    - Officer correspondence, Mary Clarke, 1979-1981 (Box 93)
    - Member survey for committee volunteers, 1974 (Box 93)
    - Correspondence, 1975-1978 (Box 144)
  - Home Economics (general)
    - Correspondence, reports, circa 1930-1959 (Box 93)
  - Home Economics Teacher Education
    - Dr. Patricia Tripple: correspondence, 1960-1970 (Box 93)
  - Home Economists in Business/Business Section
    - Affiliated chapters
      - Newsletters, 1957-1959 (Box 93)
      - Incorporation files: Colorado; Utah; Iowa; Wichita, Kansas; Twin Cities, Minnesota; Kansas City, Missouri; St. Louis, Missouri, Nebraska; Wisconsin; Connecticut; Finger Lakes Region, New York; Boston; Philadelphia; Pittsburgh, circa 1980 (Box 93)
      - Local group histories (Box 93)
      - Evansville, Indiana: minutes and financial records, 1949-1958 (Box 93)
      - Evansville, Indiana: album, 1949-1956 (Box 84)
    - Bylaws and Handbooks
      - Handbooks for Local Chairmen, 1937-1938, 1943-1945, 1958-1959 (Box 93)
      - Handbook, circa 1954 (Box 93)
      - HEIB Constitution, Bylaws and Handbook, 1957-1962 (Box 93)
      - HEIB Bylaws, 1968 (Box 93)
      - HEIB handbook (2 copies), 1971 (Box 93)
      - Executive Board handbook, 1984 (Box 93)
    - Directories
      - Membership lists, 1926-1927, circa 1930, circa 1940 (Box 93)
      - Yearbook, 1935 (Box 93)
      - HEIB directories, 1936-1952, 1969-1977, 1983-1989, 1994-1996 (Box 93)
      - Home Economists Around the World, directory (2 copies), 1984 (Box 93)
      - Directory of Consulting Business Home Economists, 1984 (Box 93)
    - Publications
      - Timely Topics, 1927-1934 (Box 64)
      - National Notes newsletter, 1954-1959 (Box 64)
      - National News Notes newsletter, 1962-1983 (Box 64)
      - Corporate Consumer Forum Trendletter, 1994 (Box 64)
      - Trends newsletter, 1995 (Box 64)
      - Brochures (Box 64)
      - Preparation for the Business Field of Home Economics, 1934, 1942 (Box 64)
      - Careers, 1954-1959, 1978-1984 (Box 64)
      - Business Career Opportunities for Home Economists, 1984, 1988 (Box 64)
      - Answers to Questions Consumers Ask about Meat and Poultry, circa 1969 (Box 64)
      - A Forward Force-The Home Economist in Business, 1985 (Box 64)
      - The Home Economist in Business, circa 1962 (Box 64)
      - Annual meeting programs, 1951-1955, 1960-1961, 1982-1983 (Box 64)
      - Annual meeting proceedings, 1975 (Box 64)
    - Correspondence, 1928 (Box 64)
    - Reports: Program of Work committee; newsletter, 1931-1932 (Box 64)
    - Canned food labeling, 1934 (Box 64)
    - Correspondence, reports, and speeches, 1945 (Box 64)
    - Investigation of Standard Measuring Cups and Measuring Spoons used in Baking, 1947-1948 (Box 64)
    - International home economists in business, 1964-1965 (Box 64)
    - Annual Meeting Speeches, reports, roundtable discussions, 1927-1948 (Box 64)
    - Reports, correspondence, 1943-1951 (Box 64)
    - Bibliographies: clothing, textiles, home furnishings, and grooming, 1950-1951 (Box 64)
    - Outline of College Courses Helpful in Training Home Economists for Business Positions, 1949-1950 (Box 64)
    - Statement of Operations, 1964 (Box 64)
    - Chair - Marjorie Child Husted, 1951-1952 (Box 64)
    - Correspondence (chair - Verna McCallum), 1957-1959 (Box 64)
    - Correspondence, 1959-1960 (Box 64)
    - Correspondence (chair - Jeanne Paris), 1960-1961 (Box 64)
    - Correspondence, 1961-1962 (Box 64)
    - Correspondence (chair - Helen Hallbert), 1962-1963 (Box 64)
    - Correspondence, 1964-1966 (Box 64)
    - Correspondence, 1962-1964 (Box 64)
    - Program Planning committee, 1967 (Box 64)
    - Program of Work, 1969 (Box 64)
    - Metric Workshop, 1976 (Box 64)
    - AHEA/HEIB relationship, 1979 (Box 64)
    - HEIB annual meeting, 1980 (Box 64)
    - HEIB Profile Study, 1975-05 (Box 64)
    - A Digest of Information Prepared for Salary Administrators, 1974 (Box 64)
    - Correspondence, 1953-1954 (Box 64)
    - Annual reports, 1967, 1980-1984 (Box 64)
    - Correspondence, 1981-1982 (Box 64)
    - Correspondence, 1983 (Box 64)
    - Correspondence, 1984 (Box 64)
    - History project correspondence, 1984 (Box 64)
    - Economics and Business Administrators Conference planning (Box 64)
    - Correspondence, reports, 1971-1973 (Box 64)
    - Correspondence, reports, 1946-1951 (Box 237)
    - Correspondence, reports, and minutes, 1954-1959 (Box 237)
    - Historical information, circa 1920-1939 (Box 237)
    - Photographs: Executive Committee meeting, 1947 (Box 237)
    - Hall of Fame program, 1993 (Box 237)
    - Bylaws, programs, and correspondence, 1981-1984 (Box 237)
    - Correspondence, 1949-1950 (Box 237)
    - Correspondence, 1978-1979 (Box 237)
    - Section brochures, pamphlets (Box 237)
    - Frequently-Asked Questions about the Business Section (Box 237)
    - Leadership workshop handouts, 1997 (Box 237)
    - Directory production, 1995-1996 (Box 237)
    - Career guide/Massachusetts Avenue building assets fund grant (Box 237)
    - Business Career Opportunities publication, 2 folders (Box 237)
    - Directory production, 1994 (Box 237)
    - Awards, 1996-1997 (Box 237)
    - Action publication, 1997 (Box 237)
    - Election, strategic planning, rules of order, 1996 (Box 237)
    - Trends, newsletter correspondence, 1995-1998 (Box 237)
    - Handouts, circa 1997 (Box 237)
    - U.S. Postal Service, correspondence, 1995-1997 (Box 237)
    - Directory production, 1993-1995 (Box 237)
    - Board of Directors correspondence, 1994 (Box 237)
    - Finances, 1994 (Box 237)
    - Correspondence, 1994-1995 (Box 237)
    - Annual meeting, 1995 (Box 237)
    - Trend letter correspondence, 1995; 2 folders (Box 237)
    - Governance information, 1994 (Box 237)
    - Board of Directors correspondence, minutes, 1993-1994 (Box 237)
    - Annual Meeting section meeting, 1993 (Box 237)
    - Board of Directors correspondence, newsletters, 1991-1993 (Box 237)
    - Reports and correspondence, 1993-1995 (Box 237)
    - Action correspondence, 1994 (Box 237)
    - HEIB member survey, 1991 (Box 237)
    - Finances; management services contracting, 1994 (Box 237)
    - HEIB 70th anniversary materials, 1994 (Box 237)
    - HEIB Membership, 1925-1983; Microfilm (Box 325)
    - Articles of Incorporation
      - California Gold Country (Box 97)
      - San Francisco (Box 97)
      - Hawaii (Box 97)
      - Big Sky Montana (Box 97)
      - Portland, Oregon (Box 97)
      - Washington State (Box 97)
      - Arizona (Box 97)
      - Los Angeles (Box 97)
      - San Diego (Box 97)
      - New York City (Box 97)
      - Chicago (Box 97)
      - Indiana (Box 97)
      - Central Michigan (Box 97)
      - Southeast Michigan (Box 97)
      - Cincinnati-Dayton (Box 97)
      - Columbus (Box 97)
      - Northeastern Ohio (Box 97)
      - National Capital Area-D.C. (Box 97)
      - Kentucky (Box 97)
      - North Carolina (Box 97)
      - East Tennessee (Box 97)
  - Home Economists in Homemaking
    - History of the section, (1973) (Box 237)
    - History of Home Economists in Homemaking 1924-1982 by Margaret Manger and Jean Taylor, (1984) (Box 237)
    - AHEA-HEIH affiliated group chairs, 1961-1969 (Box 237)
    - Chair correspondence, 1959-1965; 4 folders (Box 237)
    - Correspondence, 1941-1952, 1967-1971; 3 folders (Box 237)
    - Correspondence, Chair - E.G. Hendrickson, 1951-1952 (Box 237)
    - Correspondence, 1955-1959 (Box 237)
    - Correspondence, 1929-1946 (Box 237)
    - Correspondence and reports, 1942-1943 (Box 237)
    - Newsletters and mailing lists, 1941-1942 (Box 237)
    - Newsletters, 1938-1949; 2 folders (Box 237)
    - Newsletters, 1943-1963; 2 folders (Box 209)
    - Newsletters, circa 1972 (Box 209)
    - Articles-Concerning Careers, 1940-1942 (Box 209)
    - Fundamentals for Homemaking, 1946 (Box 209)
    - Membership lists, 1948-1949 (Box 209)
    - San Antonio Meeting newspaper clippings, 1939 (Box 209)
    - Reports and programs of work (from annual meetings), 1935-1943; 4 folders (Box 209)
    - Handbooks, 1955, 1959 (Box 209)
    - Correspondence, 1953-1954 (Box 209)
    - Correspondence, 1976-1980 (Box 144)
  - Housing and Household Equipment (also called Housing, Furnishings and Equipment)
    - Officers list (Box 209)
    - Handbook of Household Equipment Terminology, 1960, 1965 (Box 209)
    - Publications on households, 1920 (Box 209)
    - Minutes and correspondence, 1950-1965 (Box 209)
    - Housing and Equipment Laboratory, Automatic Surface Controls, 1956 (Box 209)
    - Correspondence, 1953-1954 (Box 209)
    - Correspondence, 1941-1951; 3 folders (Box 209)
    - Correspondence, 1976-1977 (Box 144)
    - Selected Bibliography on Housing, 1947 (Box 144)
    - Research Studies in Housing and Household Equipment in Colleges and Universities of the United States, 1942-1949 (Box 144)
  - Institutional Management (Institutional Administration)
    - Officers list, 1950-1964 (Box 209)
    - Correspondence and reports, 1922, 1944-1959 (Box 209)
    - Correspondence and reports, 1960-1964 (Box 209)
    - Conference proceedings, 1962-1963 (Box 209)
    - Home Economics Research in Institution Administration, 1960, 1965 (Box 209)
  - International
    - AHEA/IFHE Liaison Committee, 1971 (Box 284)
    - Correspondence, 1976-1988; 12 folders (Box 209)
    - International Exchange Committee-Ruth Ann Potts, 1977 (Box 209)
    - International exhibit and reception, correspondence, 1980-1981; 2 folders (Box 209)
    - IFHE photos, circa 1988 (Box 209)
    - Publications: women, international programs (Box 209)
    - Establishment of section: correspondence, 1973-1975 (Box 209)
    - Correspondence, 1978-1980 (Box 78)
    - Budget, 1977-1981 (Box 78)
    - Correspondence and reports, 1976-1978 (Box 78)
    - Handbook correspondence, 1979-1982 (Box 78)
    - Study Committee on International Program Structure, 1975-1977 (Box 78)
    - Grants and proposals, 1980-1981 (Box 78)
    - Workshops, 1980-1981 (Box 78)
    - Data committee, 1981 (Box 78)
    - Handbook committee, 1979-1980 (Box 78)
    - Proceedings, Income Generation for Rural Women-Jamaica Workshop, 1981 (Box 284)
    - Proceedings, Income Generation for Rural Women, 1984 (Box 78)
    - IFHE World Congress slide presentation guide, 1984 (Box 78)
    - Correspondence, Helen Strow, 1982-1983 (Box 78)
    - Correspondence and reports, 1975-1976 (Box 78)
    - Correspondence and reports, 1978-1979 (Box 78)
    - Handbook, 1980 (Box 78)
    - Treasurer reports, budget info, 1988-1991 (Box 78)
    - Program plans, correspondence, 1982-1983 (Box 78)
    - International Update (newsletter), 1977-1983; 2 folders (Box 78)
    - International Update (newsletter), 1983-1988 (Box 172)
    - Newsletter, 1989, 1991 (Box 78)
    - Policies with AHEA Home Economics implications (Box 97)
    - Handbook for AHEA International Section Chairman and the IFHE Members Organization Representative (Box 97)
    - IFHE flyers (Box 97)
    - Section officers, 1976-1990 (Box 97)
    - Ways and Means report (Box 97)
    - Up Date newsletter cost (Box 97)
    - AHEA expenses, 1989 (Box 97)
    - International Section accounting (Box 97)
    - Bazaar, 1986 (Box 97)
    - Bazaar, 1989 (Box 97)
    - AHEA Resolution IYF submitted by Committee, 26 March 1989 (Box 97)
    - Recommendations of the International Section for AHEA Strategic Planning (Box 97)
    - AHEA International Dimension, international lobbyist for AHEA (Box 97)
    - Photographs (Box 97)
    - 80th Anniversary Issues (Box 97)
    - Home Economics Contribution to International Development, 1983 (Box 97)
    - International Section seminar, 1985 (Box 97)
    - Sale of Massachusetts Ave Headquarters, 1987 (Box 97)
    - Candidates for office, 1987-1989 (Box 97)
    - Program Plan, 1987-1988 (Box 97)
    - Post IFHE World Congress Conference, Chevy Chase, MD, 1988 (Box 97)
    - IFHE committee program of work, 1988 (Box 97)
    - Research committee, 1989 (Box 97)
    - Scholarship and Exchange Program committee, 1989 (Box 97)
    - Correspondence, 1989 (Box 97)
    - Annual Meeting agenda and communications, 1989 (Box 97)
    - Gladys Gary Vaughn, 1988 (Box 97)
    - Section reports, minutes, and newsletters, 1988-1989 (Box 97)
    - Recommendation of the International Section for AHEA Strategic Planning, 1989 (Box 97)
    - Section minutes, 1989 (Box 97)
    - Reports and correspondence, 1989 (Box 97)
    - International Section Manuals, Responsibilities/Duties of IFHE AHEA Committee, 1989 (Box 97)
    - State chairs, 1988-1989 (Box 97)
    - Pre-AHEA Professional Development meeting, 1988 (Box 97)
    - Nancy B. Leidenfrost's Chair communications, 1988-1989 (Box 97)
    - Resolution, UN International Year of the Family, 1989 (Box 97)
    - Committee work, 1989 (Box 97)
    - International Section committees, 1989 (Box 97)
    - Nominating Committee, 1989 (Box 97)
    - Barbara Holt, 1989 (Box 97)
    - Nellie's gift, 1989 (Box 97)
    - Vice Chair Marilyn Prehm, 1989 (Box 97)
    - Helen Strow Scholarship Fund, 1989 (Box 97)
    - State reports, 1988-1989 (Box 97)
    - Cash receipts/disbursement journal-Peg Hoffman, 1988-1989 (Box 97)
    - Gail House, Executive Director, 1989 (Box 97)
    - AHEA IFHE History communications (Box 97)
    - AHEA/IFHE Liaison Committee, 1990 (Box 97)
    - Theme for 1996 Congress, 1991 (Box 97)
    - United States' nominations for IFHE officers and members of executive committee, 1991 (Box 97)
    - Post-AHEA Workshop, Professional Practice with a Global Perspective, 1991 (Box 97)
    - Granovsky and Weddle, AHEA, 1991 (Box 97)
    - Report of the U.S. representative on the IFHE Executive Committee, 1971 (Box 97)
    - IFHE/AHEA Committee, 1990 (Box 97)
    - AHEA IFHE Liaison, 1991 (Box 97)
    - AHEA IFHE Liaison, 1991-1993 (Box 97)
    - Nominating Committee (Nancy Granovsky, chair), IFHE/AHEA Liaison Committee, 1991 (Box 97)
    - Program for Annual Meeting, Gearing up for IYF, 1992 (Box 97)
    - Helen Strow International Fellowship Fund, 1992 (Box 97)
    - Vienna meeting, IFHE move from Paris (results of survey), 1992 (Box 97)
    - United States delegates meeting, 1992 (Box 97)
    - IFHE delegates to Council and Congress, 1992 (Box 97)
    - IFHE membership dues sent to Paris, 1992 (Box 97)
    - Correspondence, Ruth Norman (Chair, AHEA IYF Task Force and Ad Hoc Committee), 1992-1993 (Box 97)
    - International Section business, 1993-06-27 (Box 97)
    - Helen Strow, Distinguished Service Award, 1994 (Box 97)
    - International Year of the Family, 1994 (Box 97)
    - United States IFHE involvement, 1994 (Box 97)
    - "The Nature and Potentials of Home Economics as a Profession," Nancy Leidenfrost, NGO Forum, 1995 (Box 97)
    - International Division agenda/business, 1995 (Box 97)
    - IFHE-US structure, 1995 (Box 97)
    - IFHE-US structure, 1996 (Box 97)
    - IFHE-US restructuring, 1996-1997 (Box 97)
    - IFHE-US restructuring; World Food Day correspondence, 1998 (Box 97)
    - Governance and structure report planning process, 1996 (Box 97)
    - Post-AAFCS Annual Meeting IFHE Conference, 1997; 2 folders (Box 97)
    - International Division minutes, Seattle, 1999 (Box 97)
    - IFHE-US minutes, Seattle, Washington, 1999 (Box 97)
    - Memorandum of understanding, IFHE-US and AAFCS, 1999 (Box 97)
    - IFHE-US Board meeting, Chicago, 2000 (Box 56)
    - IFHE-US Board of Directors Meeting, 2001 (Box 56)
    - IFHE-US annual business meeting, Dallas, TX, 2002-06 (Box 56)
    - IFHE Representative to UN and UNICEF, 1996 (Box 56)
    - International Division, 2002 (Box 56)
    - Helen Strow Trophy, 2000 (Box 56)
    - International Division agenda, 2003 (Box 56)
    - International Section Newsletter, 1989 (Box 284)
    - International Section Newsletter UpDate-select copies, 1990-1996 (Box 56)
    - IFHE Newsletter, Paris, 1994-1995 (Box 56)
    - Journal articles, 1999-2000 (Box 56)
    - U.S. National Commission for UNESCO (Box 56)
    - Reports, 1980 (Box 56)
    - International Update, 1979-1981 (Box 56)
    - Income Generation for Rural Women workshop, 1981 (Box 56)
    - Strengthening Programs in Home Economics in the Western Hemisphere, 1979 (Box 56)
    - History and organization (Box 56)
    - Guidelines, minutes, committees, etc., 1979-1985 (Box 56)
    - International Year of the Family, 1992-1994 (Box 56)
    - Correspondence and reports, 1984-1988 (Box 28)
    - Correspondence and reports, 1989-2002 (Box 28)
    - Georgetown University conference, 1988 (Box 28)
    - Global Connections, AHEA-AID, 1986 (Box 28)
    - Strategic planning, 1989 (Box 28)
    - Seminar, 1985 (Box 28)
    - Reception guest books (Box 28)
    - International Division history (Box 28)
    - Handbook for AHEA International Section Chairpersons and IFHE Member Organization Representatives (Box 28)
    - Minutes (Box 28)
    - Section Officers Handbook (Box 28)
    - International Roles and Responsibilities for Home Economists (Box 28)
    - Miscellaneous International Division items and photographs (Box 28)
    - Program of work materials (Box 28)
    - Program details, annual meeting, 1995 (Box 28)
    - Newsletter, 1994-1995 (Box 28)
    - Annual meeting, 1994 (Box 28)
    - Program of work, 1994 (Box 28)
    - Program of work, 1995-1997 (Box 28)
    - Handbook for AHEA International Section Chairpersons and IFHE Member Organization Representatives; revisions, 5.25" disk, 1988; 1993 (Box 28)
    - Bylaws and other materials from Marian Davis (Box 28)
    - Minutes, 1994 (Box 28)
    - Accomplishment report, 1994-1995 (Box 28)
    - Resolution, 1994 (Box 28)
    - Section/division petition, 1993 (Box 28)
    - Correspondence, 1993-1995 (Box 28)
    - Workshop, 1991 (Box 28)
    - Workshops in honor of Helen Strow, annual meeting, 1994 (Box 28)
    - Workshop in honor of Helen Strow, annual meeting, 1995 (Box 28)
    - Photographs for Helen Strow, AHEA/International Section (Box 28)
    - Distinguished Service Award nomination, Helen Strow (Box 28)
    - Helen Strow International Fellowship (Box 28)
    - Miscellaneous papers from Helen Strow (Box 28)
    - International Update and other newsletters, 1977-1995; 2 folders (Box 28)
    - Expanding Global Perspectives and Actions: References and Resources, Helen Strow workshop, 1995 (Box 28)
    - Expanding Global Perspectives and Actions, Helen Strow workshop, 1995 (Box 28)
    - Professional Practices with a Global Perspective workshop, 1991 (Box 28)
    - Committees (Box 112)
    - Handbook for AHEA International Section Chairpersons and IFHE Member Organization Representatives (Box 112)
    - Development of Rural Women: Case Study of Programs of the Paraguayan Extension Service (Box 112)
    - Minutes of business meeting, 1985 (Box 112)
    - Treasurer report, 1986 (Box 112)
    - Proposed programs of work, 1987 (Box 112)
    - Reception (Box 112)
    - Minutes and financial reports, 1987-1988 (Box 112)
    - Correspondence, 1989, 1994 (Box 112)
    - Global Connections-Africa, teacher's guide and slides (Box 112)
    - Global Connections for the 1990's, NAEHE Annual Session, 1989 (Box 112)
    - Ad Hoc Strategy Planning Committee, 1990 (Box 112)
    - Recommendations of the International Section for AHEA Strategic Planning, 1989 (Box 112)
    - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1989-1990 (Box 112)
    - Program notes, 1987 (Box 112)
    - Nominating Committee, 1980-1985 (Box 112)
    - Minutes, 1980-1985 (Box 112)
    - Membership Committee, 1981-1985 (Box 112)
    - Leaders and New Faces, 1984-1985 (Box 112)
    - International Update newsletter and correspondence, 1982-1984 (Box 112)
    - Hewlett grant (Box 112)
    - Section history (Box 112)
    - Financial correspondence, 1986 (Box 112)
    - Family planning contacts, 1986 (Box 112)
    - Section committees, 1982-1987 (Box 112)
    - Business meeting agendas (Box 112)
    - International bazaar (Box 112)
    - AHEA Action schedule (Box 112)
    - Annual reports (Box 112)
    - Program of work, 1981-1986 (Box 112)
    - Project HEAP, 2 folders (Box 112)
    - Project Rural Reach (Box 112)
    - Proposal for AAHE "Role and Contributions of Home Economics in International Development" (Box 112)
    - Receptions, 1982-1987 (Box 112)
    - Section resolution, 1982-1984 (Box 112)
    - Slide project, 1984-1985 (Box 112)
    - Treasurer reports, 1982-1985 (Box 112)
    - United Nations workshop, 1985 (Box 112)
    - Home economics session at AWID meeting (Box 112)
    - Work with UNESCO, 2 folders (Box 112)
    - Business meeting, 1991 (Box 112)
    - Correspondence and reports, 1983 (Box 112)
    - Treasurer, 1988-1989 (Box 112)
    - Strategic planning, 1989 (Box 112)
    - Articles for AHEA Action, 1987-1989 (Box 112)
    - Update materials, 1989 (Box 112)
    - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1986-1987 (Box 113)
    - Update materials, 1987 (Box 113)
    - English Speaking Union/Page Scholarship (Box 113)
    - Business meeting, 1988 (Box 113)
    - Annual report, 1988 (Box 113)
    - State annual report, 1988 (Box 113)
    - Program of work, 1988-1989 (Box 113)
    - Ad Hoc Committee meeting, 1989 (Box 113)
    - International Development Conference, 1989 (Box 113)
    - Pre-AHEA International Georgetown Conference, 1988 (Box 113)
    - Program and participants, 1990 (Box 113)
    - Strategic Planning Ad Hoc Committee, 1989 (Box 113)
    - Workshop, 1989-1990 (Box 113)
    - Strategic Planning Ad Hoc Committee, 1989 (Box 113)
    - Workshop, 1991 (Box 113)
    - Case studies, 1991 (Box 113)
    - Correspondence, 1991-1994 (Box 113)
    - Workshop, 1990-1991 (Box 113)
    - IFHE/AHEA Liaison Committee, 1991 (Box 113)
    - National Briefing on International Development: Implications for Home Economists, 1988; 3 folders (Box 113)
    - Workshop reports, 1991 (Box 113)
    - Strategic Planning Phase II Ad Hoc Committee, 1991-1992 (Box 113)
    - Correspondence, 1982-1984 (Box 113)
    - Workshop, 1990-1991 (Box 113)
    - Professional Practices with a Global Perspective workshop, 1991 (Box 113)
    - AHEA Strategic Planning, 1989 (Box 113)
    - Strategic planning, 1991 (Box 113)
    - Strategic planning, 1990-1991 (Box 113)
    - Section meeting, March 1989 (Box 113)
    - UNESCO Co-Action workshops, 1980-1981 (Box 113)
    - Correspondence and workshop information, 1980-1983 (Box 113)
    - IFHE-AAFCS Liaison Committee, 1995-1996 (Box 113)
    - IFHE-AHEA-AAFCS Liaison Committee, International Division agendas, correspondence, handbooks, 1977-2005 (Box 138)
    - Different but Alike: Universality of Women Worldwide (Box 138)
    - International Group becoming a Subject Matter Section - Correspondence, 1976 (Box 332)
    - International Section Annual Meeting Minutes, 1976-1979 (Box 332)
    - International Section Annual Meeting Minutes, 1980-1989 (Box 332)
    - International Section Annual Meeting Minutes, 1990-1995 (Box 332)
    - International Division Annual Meeting Minutes, 1997-2003 (Box 332)
    - International Division - Treasurer's Report, 1998-2004 (Box 332)
    - Helen Strow's Induction, 1999 (Box 332)
    - Tax Exempt Number, 1990 (Box 332)
    - IFHE Campaign, Development Fund, Development Goals, 2011-2014 (Box 332)